{
    "subject": "resource/Sexual_intercourse",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Sexual intercourse",
    "human_readable": "The label for Sexual intercourse is Sexual intercourse.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9539552927017212,
            "question": "What is the label for Sexual intercourse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6726014018058777,
            "question": "Is 'Sexual intercourse' a type of activity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6165383458137512,
            "question": "What are some common contexts in which the term 'Sexual intercourse' is used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5915544629096985,
            "question": "Can you provide a synonym for 'Sexual intercourse'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5336403846740723,
            "question": "What social or cultural norms surround 'Sexual intercourse'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5079178810119629,
            "question": "How does 'Sexual intercourse' relate to concepts like love, intimacy, and relationships?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5019789338111877,
            "question": "What are the potential consequences of engaging in 'Sexual intercourse'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4814053177833557,
            "question": "How is 'Sexual intercourse' portrayed in different media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47543007135391235,
            "question": "What are some of the physical and emotional aspects associated with 'Sexual intercourse'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4251059591770172,
            "question": "Are there any legal or ethical considerations related to 'Sexual intercourse'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label for Sexual intercourse is Sexual intercourse.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5797_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the physical and emotional aspects associated with 'Sexual intercourse'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5797_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is 'Sexual intercourse' portrayed in different media?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5797_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the potential consequences of engaging in 'Sexual intercourse'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5797_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5797_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, \"Sexual intercourse\" is mentioned as a topic in several files (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5797/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5797/re-ranker-msmarco/71.txt), and it is also mentioned as the label for a section in one of the files (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5797/re-ranker-msmarco/71.txt). Therefore, the triple is correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents do indeed support the information that \"Sexual intercourse\" is labeled as \"Sexual intercourse.\" Each document consistently refers to the term and its definitions or descriptions."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}